Guide to the Child Study Center, School of Medicine, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Donald J. Cohen as director, 1970-2001; Accession 2002-A-211
  - Articles written by Dr. Cohen
    - Segregation And Linkage Analyses Of Gilles De La Tourette's Syndrome And Related Disorders. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1990) (Box 2)
    - Human Platelet Dense Granules: Improved Isolation And Preliminary Characterization Of [3H]-Serotonin Uptake And Tetrabenazine-Displaceable [3H]-Ketanserin Binding. Life Sciences (1990) (Box 2)
    - Enduring Sadness: Early Loss, Vulnerability And The Shaping Of Character. Psychoanalytic Study Of The Child (1990) (Box 2)
    - Intellectual, Academic, And Adaptive Functioning Of Tourette Syndrome Children With And Without Attention Deficit Disorder. Journal Of Abnormal Child Psychology (1990) (Box 2)
    - Establishing The Reliability And Validity Of Neuropsychological Disorders With Low Base Rates: Some Recommended Guidelines. Journal Of Clinical And Experimental Neuropsychology (1991) (Box 2)
    - Reproducibility And Temporal Stability Of ADP-Induced Platelet Aggregation: Comparison Of The Anticoagulants Sodium Citrate And D-Phenylalanyl-L-Proly-L-Arginyl-Chloromethyl Ketone. American Journal Of Hematology (1991) (Box 2)
    - Co-Morbid Association Of Autism And Schizophrenia. American Journal Of Psychiatry (Box 2)
    - The Child Psychoanalytic Play Interview: A Technique For Studying Thematic Content. Journal Of The American Psychoanalytic Association (1991) (Box 2)
    - Postural Control In Autistic Children. Journal Of Autism And Developmental Disorders (1992) (Box 2)
    - The Development Of A Capacity For Imagination In Early Childhood. Psychoanalytic Study Of The Child (1992) (Box 2)
    - Clomipramine Improving Obsessive-Compulsive, Aggressive, And Social-Interactive Phenomena In Autistic Young Adults (1992) (Box 2)
    - Play In Psychoanalysis And Development. Bulletin Of The Anna Freud Centre (1992) (Box 2)
    - Three Diagnostic Systems For Autism: DSM-III, DSM-III-R, And ICD-10. Journal Of Autism And Developmental Disorders (1992) (Box 2)
    - Brief Report: Developmental Aspects Of DSM-III-R Criteria For Autism. Journal Of Autism And Developmental Disorders (1992) (Box 2)
    - Le Syndrome De Tourette: Psychopathologie Du Developpement Dans Un Modele De Dysfonctionement Neuropsychiatrique De L'enfant. La Psychiatrie De l'Enfant (1992) (Box 2)
    - Death Without Warning? A Clinical Post-Mortem Study Of 43 Israeli Adolescent Male Suicides. Archives Of General Psychiatry (1993) (Box 2)
    - Premonitory Urges In Tourette's Syndrome. American Journal Of Psychiatry (1993) (Box 2)
    - Integrating Biological And Behavioral Perspectives In The Study And Care Of Autistic Individuals: The Future. Israel Journal Of Psychiatry (1993) (Box 2)
    - Acute Tryptophan Depletion In Autistic Disorder: A Controlled Case Study. Biological Psychiatry (1993) (Box 2)
    - Conceptualizing "Borderline Syndrome Of Childhood" And "Childhood Schizophrenia" As A Developmental Disorder. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1993) (Box 2)
    - CSF Monoamine Precursors And Metabolites In Human Neonates Following In Utero Cocaine Exposure: A Preliminary Study. Pediatrics (1993) (Box 2)
    - An Epidemiological Study Of Gilles De La Tourette's Syndrome In Israel. Archives Of General Psychiatry (1993) (Box 2)
    - The Familial Relationship Between Gilles De La Tourette's Syndrome, Attention Deficit Disorder, Learning Disabilities, Speech Disorders And Stuttering. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1993) (Box 2)
    - Recent Research In Autism. Child And Adolescent Psychiatric Clinics Of North America (1993) (Box 2)
    - Autism: Current Concepts. Child And Adolescent Psychiatric Clinics Of North America (1994) (Box 2)
    - Playing And Therapeutic Action In Child Analysis. International Journal Of Psychoanalysis (1993) (Box 2)
    - Experiencing Self And Others: Contributions From Studies Of Autism To The Psychoanalytic Theory Of Social Development. Journal Of The American Psychoanalytic Association (1993) (Box 2)
    - The Social Matrix Of Aggression: Enactments And Representations Of Loving And Hating In The First Years Of Life. Psychoanalytic Study Of The Child (1993) (Box 2)
    - Corpus Callosum Morphology From Magnetic Resonance Images In Tourette's Syndrome. Psychiatry Research: Neuroimaging (1994) (Box 2)
    - Abnormal Magnetic Resonance Imaging T2Relaxation Time Asymmetries In Tourette's (Box 2)
    - Syndrome. Psychiatry Research: Neuroimaging (1994) (Box 2)
    - The Effect Of Humor On Children's Developing Theory Of Mind. British Journal Of Developmental Psychology (1994) (Box 2)
    - Field Trial For Autistic Disorder In DSM-Iv. American Journal Of Pschiatry (1994) (Box 2)
    - Psychosocial Therapies For Children And Adolescents: Overview And Future Directions. Journal Of Abnormal Child Psychology (1995) (One copy and some letters) (Box 2)
    - A Case-Controlled Study Of Repetitive Thoughts And Behaviors In Adults With Autistic Disorder And Obsessive Compulsive Disorder. American Journal Of Psychiatry (1995) (Box 2)
    - Multiplex Developmental Disorder. Journal Of Developmental And Behavioral Pediatrics: Special Issue On Young Children With Developmental Delay (1995) (Box 2)
    - Tic-Related Vs. Non-Tic-Related Obsessive Compulsive Disorder. Anxiety (1995) (Box 2)
    - An Epidemiological Study Of Trichotillomania In Israeli Adolescents. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry(1995) (Box 2)
    - Plasma Androgens In Autism. Journal Of Autism And Developmental Disorders (1995) (Box 2)
    - Ethical Issues In Biological Mental Health Research With Children and Adolescents. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1995) (Box 2)
    - Acute And Chronic Effects Of Fluoxetine And Haloperidol On Mouse Brain Serotonin And Norepinephrine Turnover. Life Sciences (1995) (Box 2)
    - Asperger's Syndrome. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1995) (Box 2)
    - Effects Of Special Olympics International On Social Competence In Persons With Mental Retardation. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1996) (Box 2)
    - Israeli Preschoolers Under Scud Missile Attacks: A Developmental Perspective On Risk-Modifying Factors. Archives Of General Psychiatry (1996) (Box 2)
    - Children's Developing Theory Of Mind. Journal Of The American Psychoanalytic Association (1996). (Box 2)
    - Linkage Disequilibrium Between An Allele At The Dopamine D4 Receptor Locus With Tourette's Syndrome By TDT. American Journal Of Human Genetics (1996). (Box 2)
    - A Double-Blind Placebo-Controlled Study Of Fluvoxamine In Adults With Autistic Disorder. Archives Of General Psychiatry (1996). (Box 2)
    - Anna Freud And Developmental Psychoanalytic Psychology. Psychoanalytic Study Of The Child (1996). (Box 2)
    - G.R., Price, L.H. (1996), Effects Of Tryptophan Depletion In Drug-Free Adults With Autism. Archives Of General Psychiatry (1996). (Box 2)
    - Test-Retest Reliability For False-Belief Tasks. Journal Of Child Psychology And Psychiatry (1996). (Box 2)
    - Sertraline In Adults With Pervasive Developmental Disorders. Journal Of Clinical Psychopharmacology. (1996) (Box 2)
    - Tic Disorders. Psychiatric Clinics Of North America (1997). (Box 2)
    - Israeli Preschool Children Under Scuds: A 30 Month Follow-Up. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry. (1997) (Box 2)
    - The Treatment Of Tourette's Syndrome: Multimodal, Developmental Intervention. Journal Of Clinical Psychiatry (1998) (Box 2)
    - Police And Mental Health Professionals: Collaborative Responses To The Impact Of Violence On Children And Families. Child And Adolescent Psychiatric Clinics Of North America. (1998) (Box 2)
    - A Double-Blind,Placebo-Controlled Study Of Risperidone In Adults With Autistic Disorder And Other Pervasive Developmental Disorders. Archives Of General Psychiatry. (1998) (Box 2)
    - Developmental Psychopathology: A Framework For Planning Child Mental Health. Epidemiologia E Psichiatria Sociale. (1997) (Box 2)
    - A Preliminary Study Of The Effects Of Tryptophan Depletion On Tics, Obsessive Compulsive Symptoms, And Mood In Tourette's Syndrome. Biological Psychiatry,(1997) (Box 2)
    - Effects Of Diagnosis, Race, And Pubertal Status On Platelet Serotonin Levels In Autism And Mental Retardation. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child and Adolescent Psychiatry (1998) (Box 2)
    - Multiplex Developmental Disorders: The Role Of Communication In The Construction Of A Self. Psychiatric Clinics Of North America (1999) (Box 2)
    - Etude Des Conduites Auto-Agressives, De La Reactivite A La Douleur Et De Leurs Interrelations Chez Les Enfants Autistes. L'encéphale (1999) (Box 2)
    - Preliminary Findings Of Antistreptococcal Antibody Titers And Basal Ganglia Volumes In Tic, Obsessive-Compulsive, And Attention-Deficit/Hyperactivity Disorders. Archives Of General Psychiatry (2000) (Box 2)
    - Abnormal Ventral Temporal Cortical Activity During Face Discrimination Among Individuals With Autism And Asperger Syndrome. Archives Of General Psychiatry. (2000) (Box 2)
    - "Who's Afraid Of Virginia Woolf?" And Autism: A Case Study Of Social Visual Pursuit. American Journal Of Psychiatry (In Press) One Copy and some photographs (Box 2)
    - Developmental Psychopathology: Research, Clinical Care And Social Policy. Israel Journal Of Psychiatry And Related Science (2000), computer file (DOC)
      General note
      Contact Public Services (phone: 203 432-1735, e-mail: mssa.reference@yale.edu) for information on accessing this digital object.
    - The Mother-Child Dyad Facing Trauma: A Developmental Outlook. Journal Of Nervous Mental Disorders (2000) (Box 2)
    - Visual-Motor Integration Functioning In Children With Tourette Syndrome. Neuropsychology. (1998) (Box 2)
    - Mothers' Functioning And Children's Symptoms 5 Years After A Scud Missile Attack. American Journal Of Psychiatry. (2001) (Box 2)
    - A Placebo-Controlled Study Of Guanfacine In The Treatment Of Children With Tic Disorders And Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder. American Journal Of Psychiatry (2001) (Box 2)
    - Guanfacine In The Treatment Of Children With Tic Disorders And Adhd: A Placebo-Controlled Study. American Journal Of Psychiatry. (20001 (Box 2)
    - Regional Brain And Ventricular Volumes In Tourette Syndrome. Archives Of General Psychiatry. (2001) (Box 2)
  - Chapters written by Dr. Cohen
    - The Impact Of Skin Disease On The Person. In: Dermatology In General Medicine, T. Fitzpatrick (Ed.). New York: Mcgraw Hill (1970) (Box 3)
    - Competence And Biology: Methodology In Studies Of Infants, Twins, Psychosomatic Disease, And Psychosis. In: The Child In His Family: Children At Psychiatric Risk, E. J. Anthony And C. Koupernik (Eds.). New York: John Wiley and Sons (1974) (Box 3)
    - Psychosomatic Models Of Development. In: Explorations In Child Psychiatry, E. James Anthony (Ed.). New York: Plenum Publishing Corporation (1975) (Box 3)
    - Preadolescence: A Critical Phase Of Biological And Psychological Development. In: Mental Health In Children-Psychiatric And Psychological Problems, Vol. I, D.V.Siva Sankar (Ed.). Westbury, New York: PJD Publications Ltd (1975) (Box 3)
    - Mental Health Services. In: Issues In The Classification Of Children: A Sourcebook On Categories, Labels, And Their Consequences, N. Hobbs (Ed.). San Francisco, Ca: Jossey-Bass Publishers (1975) (Box 3)
    - Minimal Brain Dysfunction: Diagnosis And Therapy. In: Current Psychiatric Therapies, Vol. 17, J. H. Masserman (Ed.). New York: Grune and Stratton (Box 3)
    - Neurochemical And Developmental Models Of Childhood Autism. In: Cognitive Defects In The Development Of Mental Illness, G. Serban (Ed.). New York: Brunner/Mazel (1978) (Box 3)
    - Methodological Issues In Twin Research: The Assumption Of Environmental Equivalence. In: Twin Research: Psychology And Methodology, G. Allen (Ed.). New York: Alan R. Liss, Inc (1978) (Box 3)
    - The Molecular Biology Of Development. In: Basic Handbook Of Child Psychiatry, Vol. I, J. Noshpitz (Ed.). New York: Basic Books (1979) No Chapter. Only some figures in an envelope. (Box 3)
    - Day Care In America. In: The Child And Society: Essays In Applied Child Development, D. Elkind (Ed.). Fairlawn, Nj: Oxford University Press (1979) (Box 3)
    - Cerebrospinal Fluid Monoamine Metabolites In Neurological Disorders Of Childhood. In: Neurobiology Of Cerebrospinal Fluid, Vol. 1, J. H. Wood (Ed.). New York: Plenum Publishing Corporation (1980) (Box 3)
    - The Interplay Of Biological Endowment, Early Experience, And Psychosocial Influence During The First Year Of Life: An Epidemiological Twin Study. In: The Child In His Family: Preventive Child Psychiatry In An Age Of Transition, E. J. Anthony And C. Chiland (Eds.). (1980) (Box 3)
    - Mania In Childhood And Adolescence. In: Mania: An Evolving Concept, R. H. Belmaker And H. M. Van Praag (Eds.). Jamaica, Ny: Spectrum Publications, Inc. (1980) (Box 3)
    - The Pathology Of The Self In Primary Childhood Autism And Gilles De La Tourette Syndrome. In: Psychiatric Clinics Of North America, Vol. 3, No. 3, B. Blinder (Ed.). Philadelphia: W.B. Saunders Company (1980) (Box 3)
    - Neurochemical And Behavioral Organization: Disorders Of Attention, Activity, And Aggression. In: Vulnerabilities To Delinquency, D. O. Lewis (Ed.). New York: Sp Medical and Scientific Books (1981) (Box 3)
    - Neurobiological Approaches To The Treatment Of Children With Severe Psychiatric Disorders. In: Advances In Human Psychopharmacology, Vol. 2, G. D. Burrows And J. S. Werry (eds.). Greenwich, CT: JAI Press, Inc (1981) (Box 3)
    - The Emergence Of Meanings And Intentions: Mothers' Dialogue With Normal And Language-Impaired Children. Psychiatric Clinics Of North America (1981) (Box 3)
    - Interaction Of Biological And Psychological Factors In The Natural History Of Tourette's Syndrome: A Paradigm For Childhood Neuropsychiatric Disorders. In: Advances In Neurology, Vol. 35, Gilles De La Tourette Syndrome, T. N. Chase and A. J. Friedhoff (Eds.). New York: Raven Press (1982) (Box 3)
    - The Relationship Between Borderline Syndromes And Attention Deficit Disorders Of Childhood: Clinical And Neurochemical Perspectives. In: The Borderline Child, K. S. Robson (Ed.). New York: Mcgraw-Hill (1982) (Box 3)
    - Biochemical Influences In Attention Deficit Disorder (Add): Results From Human And Animal Investigations. In: Topics In Child Neurology, G. Wise, M. Blaw, and P. G. Procopis (Eds.). New York: Spectrum Publications (1983) (Box 3)
    - Clinical Studies Of Mhpg In Childhood And Adolescence. In: MHPG And Psychopathology, J. W. Maas (Ed.). New York: Academic Press (1983) (Box 3)
    - Developmental Language Studies In The Neuropsychiatric Disorders Of Childhood. In: Children's Language, K. E. Nelson (Ed.). New York: Gardner Press, Inc (1983) (Box 3)
    - Biological Research On Depression In Childhood. In: Affective Disorders In Childhood And Adolescence, D. P. Cantwell (Ed.). New York: Spectrum Publication (1983) (Box 3)
    - Repetitive Behaviors Of Childhood. In: Developmental-Behavioral Pediatrics, M. Levine and W. Carey (Eds.). Philadelphia: W. B. Saunders (1983, 1991) (Box 3)
    - Pharmacotherapy Of Attention Deficit Disorders. In: Pediatrics Update, Vol. 5, A. Moss (Ed.). North Holland: Elsevier (1983) (Box 3)
    - Psychiatric Problems Of Childhood. In: Psychiatry In The Practice Of Medicine, H. Leigh (Ed.). New York: Addison and Wesley Publishing Co (1983) (Box 3)
    - Psychiatric Problems Of Adolescence. In: Psychiatry In The Practice Of Medicine, H. Leigh (Ed.). New York: Addison and Wesley Publishing Co. (1983) (Box 3)
    - Developmental And Pharmacological Aspects Of Attention Deficit Disorder. In: Developmental Pharmacology, S. M. Macleod (Ed.). New York: Alan R. Liss, Inc. (1983) (Box 3)
    - The Tourette Syndrome and Other Tics. In: A Clinical Guide To Child Psychiatry. D. Shaffer, A. A. Ehrhardt, and L. Greenhill (Eds.). New York: Macmillan Free Press (1984) (Box 3)
    - Multi-Modal Treatment Of Add, Pediatric Clinics Of North America, Shaywitz, S.E., Grossman, H., Shaywitz, B.A., (Eds.) (1984) (Box 3)
    - Neurotransmitter Ontogeny As A Perspective For Studies Of Child Development And Pathology. In: The Psychobiology Of Childhood: A Profile Of Current Issues, B. Shopsin and L. Greenhill (Eds.). New York: Spectrum Publications (1984) (Box 3)
    - Psychiatric Aspects Of Learning Difficulties, Pediatric Clinics Of North America, Shaywitz, S.E., Grossman, H., Shaywitz, B.A., (Eds.) (1984) (Box 3)
    - Early Brain Damage And Attentional Deficit Disorder: An Animal Model. In: Early Brain Damage, Almli, C.R., Ginger, S. (Eds.)., Orlando: Academic Press, Inc (1984) (Box 3)
    - Neurochemical Correlates Of Attention Deficit Disorder. In: Pediatric Clinics Of North America, Shaywitz, S.E., Grossman, H., Shaywitz, B.A., (Eds.) (1984) (Box 3)
    - Tourette's Syndrome And Tic Disorders. In: Psychopharmacology Of Childhood And Adolescence, Weiner, J.M., (Ed.), New York:John Wiley and Sons, Inc (1985) (Box 3)
    - Clinical Neurochemical Strategies In Child Psychiatry. In: Psychiatry, Cavenar, J.O. and Michels, R. (Eds.), Lippincott Co., Volume 2, Chapter 12 (1985) (Box 3)
    - Pervasive Developmental Disorders. In: Psychiatry, Cavenar, J. O. and Michels, R. (Eds.) Philadelphia: Lippincott Co., Volume 2:Chapter 27 (1985) (Box 3)
    - Cerebrospinal Fluid Monoamine Precursor And Metabolite Levels In Children Treated For Leukemia: Age And Sex Effects And Individual Variablity. In: Biological Psychiatry, Wortis, J. (Ed.), New York: Elsevier (1986) (Box 3)
    - Autism. In: World Book Encyclopedia (1986) (Box 3)
    - Research In Child Psychiatry: Lines Of Personal, Institutional And Career Development. In: Clinical Research Careers In Child Psychiatry. H.A. Pincus And H. Pardes (Eds.). Washington, D.C.: American Psychiatric Association (1986) (Box 3)
    - Tourette Syndrome: Clinical Features, Etiology And Pathogenesis. In: Basic Handbook Of Child X Psychiatry, Vol. V. Advances And New Directions, J. D. Noshpitz (Ed.). New York: Basic Books, Chapter (1987) (Some correspondence letters and) (Box 3)
    - Neuropsychiatric Problems In Children Treated For Leukemia: An Iatrogenic Model Of Attention Deficit Disorder. In: Advances In Human Psychopharmacology, Vol.Iv, Werry, J.S. and Burrows, G.D. (Eds.). Jai Press, Greenwich, CT (1987) (Box 3)
    - Classification And Diagnosis Of Childhood Autism: Empirical Studies And Diagnostic Criteria. In: Colloque Inserm. Vol. 146. F. Gremy, S. Tomkiewicz, P. Ferrari, G. Lelord (Eds.). Paris (1987) (Box 3)
    - Neurotransmitters In Human Epilepsy. In: Neurotransmitters And Epilepsy, Jobe, P.C. (Ed.), Humana Press (1987) (Box 3)
    - Developmental Neuropharmacology: Clinical And Neurochemical Perspectives On The Regulation Of Attention, Learning And Movement. In: Handbook Of Psychopharmacology, Volume 19. L.L. Iversen, S.D. Iversen, And S.H. Snyder, (Eds.). New York: Plenum Press (1988) (Box 3)
    - Classification And Diagnosis Of Childhood Autism. In: Diagnosis And Assessment In Autism. E. Schopler and G. Mesibov (Eds.). New York: Plenum Press (1988) (Box 3)
    - The Diagnostic Process And Classification In Child Psychiatry: Issues And Prospects. In: International Classification In Psychiatry, Mezzich, J. and Von Cranach, M. (Eds.). Cambridge: Cambridge University Press, Chapter 24 (1988) (Box 3)
    - The Diagnosis And Classification Of Autism: Empirical Studies Relevant To Nosology. In: International Classification In Psychiatry, Mezzich, J. and Von Cranach, M. (Eds.). Cambridge: Cambridge University Press, Chapter 10 (1988) (Box 3)
    - The Clinical Care Of Individuals With Tourette's Syndrome. In: Tourette's Syndrome And Tic Disorders: Clinical Understanding And Treatment. D.J. Cohen, R.D. Bruun and J.F. Leckman (Eds.). New York: John Wiley and Sons, Inc (1988) (Box 3)
    - Descriptive And Diagnostic Classification Of Tic Disorders. In: Tourette's Syndrome And Tic Disorders: Clinical Understanding And Treatment. D.J. Cohen, R.D. Bruun and J.F. Leckman (Eds.). New York: John Wiley and Sons, Inc (1988) (Box 3)
    - Clonidine Treatment Of Tourette's Syndrome. In: Tourette's Syndrome And Tic Disorders: Clinical Understanding And Treatment. D.J. Cohen, R.D. Bruun and J.F. Leckman (Eds.). New York: John Wiley and Sons, Inc (1988) (Box 3)
    - Clinical Assessment Of Tic Disorder Severity. In: Tourette's Syndrome And Tic Disorders: Clinical Understanding And Treatment. D.J. Cohen, R.D. Bruun, and J.F. Leckman (Eds.). New York: John Wiley and Sons, Inc. (1988) (Box 3)
    - Family Functioning And Tourette's Syndrome. In: Tourette's Syndrome And Tic Disorders: Clinical Understanding And Treatment. D.J. Cohen, R.D. Bruun, and J.F. Leckman (Eds.). New York: John Wiley and Sons, Inc (1988) (Box 3)
    - Diagnosis Of Pervasive Developmental Disorders. In: Advances In Clinical Child Psychology, Vol. 11. A.E. Kazdin and B.B. Lahey (Eds.). Pittsburg: Plenum Publishing, Chapter (1988) (Box 3)
    - Attentional And Neurochemical Components Of Mental Retardation: New Methods For An Old Problem. In: Retardation And Mental Health. J.A. Stark, F.J. Menolascino, M.H. Albarelli and V.C. Gray (Eds.). New York: Springer-Verlag (1988) (Box 3)
    - Mental Disorders And Psychopharmacology Of Retarded Persons: Another Step In Seeing The Whole Person. In: Understanding Mental Retardation: Research Accomplishments And New Frontiers, Chapter 22. J.F. Kavanagh (Ed.). Baltimore: Paul H. Brookes Publishing Co. (1988) (Box 3)
    - Tourette's Syndrome: A Model Developmental, Neuropsychiatric Disorder. In: The Child And His Family. C. Chiland And J.G. Young (Eds.). Paris: Presse Universitaire De France (1989) (Box 3)
    - Tic Disorders: Phenomenology, Diagnosis, And Assessment. In: Treatments Of Psychiatric Disorders. T.B. Karasu (Ed.). A Task Force Report Of The American Psychiatric Association, Washington, D.C.: Appi, Section 8, Chapter (1989) (Box 3)
    - Deviance And Developmental Approaches In The Study Of Autism. In: Issues In The Developmental Approach To Mental Retardation. R. Hodapp, J. Burack And E. Zigler, (Eds.). Cambridge University Press, Chapter 10 (1990) (Box 3)
    - Infantile Autism: Diagnosis, Assessment, And Intervention. In: Les Strategies Therapeutiques Appliquees Dans L'autism Infantiles. P. Parquet, C. Burstejn, B. Golse (Eds.). Paris: Masson Eds, Chapter 11 (1990) (Box 3)
    - Biochemical And Genetic Studies Of Tourette's Syndrome. In: Application Of Basic Neuroscience To Child Psychiatry, S. Deutsch, A. Weizman, R. Weizman (Eds.). New York: Plenum Publishing Corporation, Chapter 14 (1990) (Box 3)
    - The Hyperserotonemia Of Autism. The Neuropharmacology Of Serotonin, Annals Of The New York Academy Of Sciences (1990) (Box 3)
    - Non-Autistic Pervasive Developmental Disorder. In: Psychiatry, Volume 6, R. Michels, J.O.Cavenar, Jr., (Eds.). A.J. Solnit, D.J. Cohen, J.E. Schowalter (Section Eds.). Philadelphia:J.B. Lippincott Co. Chapter 27.2 (1991) (Box 3)
    - The Diagnosis And Assessment Of Tic Disorders. In: Child Psychopathology: Diagnostic Criteria And Clinical Assessment. S. Hooper, G. Hynd, R. Mattison (Eds.). New Jersey: Lawrence Erlbaum Associates, Inc., Chapter 10 (1992) (Box 3)